# Karan Dasari

Email: krn.sd7276@gmail.com Contact: 9518346947

# **EDUCATION**

# P.E.S.MCOE, PUNE

B.E IN COMPUTER ENGG. 2017-20 | Pune,India CGPA: 7.23

# **GOVT.POLYTECHNIC.SOLAPUR**

DIPLOMA IN COMPUTER ENGG. 2014-17 | Solapur, India Percentage: 79.8

# SUYASH CENTRAL SCHOOL, SO-LAPUR

10TH STANDARD 2013-14 | Solapur, India CGPA: 8.4

# LINKS

LinkedIn: karandasari Github: karan7276 HackerRank:karan7276 Codechef: karankd<sub>1</sub>23

# SKILLS

#### **PROGRAMMING**

- (++
- Python
- JAVA

# **FRONT-END**

• HTML • CSS • JavaScript

#### **DATABASES**

• MySQL • NoSQL

#### **TOOLS**

• Jenkins • Postman

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Winner in C Booster Competition at District Level.
- Was a Team Member of Smart City, Solapur.
- Got triggered to Google Foobar while searching problems on google and successfully completed Level 3.
- Global Rank 1790 in August Long Challenge Codechef. 2020

# **PROFILE**

A computer science enthusiast having programming experiences in languages like C,C++,Python.In-depth knowledge of designing and development tools and coding languages.Almost 1 year of work experience in innovating software designs, testing and coding as well as debugging programs

# **EXPERIENCE**

# **TIBCO SOFTWARE**

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

March 2020 - April 2022 | Pune, India

• Part of a team on the product named Jaspersoft (Jaspersoft software lets you easily create a self-service reporting environment where users can create their own.)

#### MARKETPLUG UK

BACKEND JAVA DEVELOPER

April 2022 - Present | London, United Kingdom

• Part of a backend team where we are developing the Marketplug product from scratch

# **PROJECTS**

# DETECTION OF DIABETIC EYE DISEASE USING THERMAL IMAGES USING CNN ALGORITHM

• To analysis and investigation of retinal diseases in the primary stage through data mining techniques that make the decision making process useful.

#### **SELENIUM ON PAYTM**

Link-Selenium On Paytm

- An Automation Testing on Paytm Website which automatically allows you to add money in your Paytm wallet from Paytm bank account using Selenium Framework...
- Developed using Python and Selenium framework.

# **QUESTION PAPER GENERATION**

GENERATING QUESTION PAPERS ON THE GO

• A Website that accepts the questions from user with respect to bloom's taxonomy level. Lets user to select questions, which should be in question paper and generates question paper in PDF format.

# INTERESTS

CRYPTO MARKETING.

VOLUNTEER WORK.

LISTENING TO MUSIC.

TRAVELLING.